Alex Buhai

 $\frac{368-299-7666 \mid \underline{oleksandr.buugay@gmail.com} \mid \underline{https://www.linkedin.com/in/alex-buhai-95a35227b} \mid \underline{https://github.com/OleksandrBuhai}$

Summary

Front-End Developer with over one year of experience, specializing in React, TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS. I pursued my education at NTUU KPI, with a background in Manufacturing Engineering, and further enhanced my skills through various IT courses such as IT-Incubator.io.

EDUCATION

IT-Incubator.io

Front-End Developer May 2020 - May 2021

NTUU KPI

Aug. 2015 - May 2019

Studied Manufacturing Engineering IPTKisSUMDU

Konotop, Ukraine

Kyiv, Ukraine

College Degree in Manufacturing Technology

May 2013 - May 2015

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

Apr 2023 - Jul 2023

Remote

Berlin Labs LLC
• Development of small features

• Participation in the development of a project for the sale of photo \ video.

• Markup

• Fix Bugs

Front-End Developer

Jun 2022 - Mar 2023

Mladá Boleslav, CZ

Self employ

• Development of landing pages;

• Development of small features

• Participation in the development of a project for the sale of photo \ video.

• Markup

• Fix Bugs

Production Supervisor

May 2019 - Dec 2021

Škoda Auto

Mladá Boleslav, CZ

- Addressing technical challenges
- Managed both equipment and a team, ensuring smooth operations and quality standards
- Addressing technical challenges

Graphic Assistant

Mindy Support

Dec 2016 – Jul 2017

Kyiv, Ukraine

- Data Processing for Neural Networks
- Image Processing for Future Use

PROJECTS

Portfolio | React, JavaScript, CSS

- https://oleksandrbuhai.github.io/Portfolio/
- Developed a responsive portfolio web site using React
- Deployment on GitHub Pages
- Working with libraries framer-motion, React styled component, tsparticles

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Lanuages: English, Czech, Ukranian

ProgLanguages: JavaScript, TypeScript HTML/CSS

Frameworks: React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Next. js, Tailwind CSS, Material-UI

Developer Tools: Git, Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ